<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Off-Hours</title>
    <link>http://newtux.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Off-Hours</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:27:53 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://newtux.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes for How Can a Strategy Everyone Knows About Still Work?</title>
      <link>http://newtux.github.io/posts/how_can_a_strategy_everyone_knows_about_still_work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 00:27:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newtux.github.io/posts/how_can_a_strategy_everyone_knows_about_still_work/</guid>
      <description>Paper Link
Any systematic strategy works for two basic reasons (though these do not have to be mutually exclusive):
 Risk Premium: You are receiving a proper risk premium (i.e. for stocks with higher expected risks, you get higher expected returns). You risk loss at times when that loss is most painful. Behavioral: Investors make errors, or at least do not act &amp;ldquo;rationally&amp;rdquo;.  So what happens then when a strategy becomes &amp;ldquo;known&amp;rdquo;:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keeping Track of The Arrow Ecosystem</title>
      <link>http://newtux.github.io/posts/keeping_track_of_the_arrow_ecosystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 20:12:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newtux.github.io/posts/keeping_track_of_the_arrow_ecosystem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;http://arrow.apache.org/&#34;&gt;Arrow&lt;/a&gt; ecosystem keeps growing and getting better (which is exciting) but I can never really remember which part is supposed to do what.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m terribly sorry for a lot of over simplification here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An R Anlysis of the Beer Advocate Dataset</title>
      <link>http://newtux.github.io/posts/beer_reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 14:35:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newtux.github.io/posts/beer_reviews/</guid>
      <description>Inspired by the LinkedIn post https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/how-hire-test-data-skills-one-size-fits-all-interview-tanya-cashorali/, my attempt to explore the dataset and see what’s there.
Questions: Which brewery produces the strongest beers by ABV%? If you had to pick 3 beers to recommend using only this data, which would you pick? Which of the factors (aroma, taste, appearance, palette) are most important in determining the overall quality of a beer? Lastly, if I typically enjoy a beer due to its aroma and appearance, which beer style should I try?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimenting with WordVectors and Codenames</title>
      <link>http://newtux.github.io/posts/codenames-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 21:29:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://newtux.github.io/posts/codenames-part-1/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing a lot of Codenames and came across https://jamesmullenbach.github.io/2018/01/02/codenames-fun.html which explored using word2vec to generate clue words. This was really cool! I started wondering if we could use a similar approach to actually play as a spymaster, i.e. answering the question:
Given a game board and a side, what should my clue word + targeted number be?
This post is a collection of some things I tried and the results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>